Forever is harder than it looks.
The Old Guard is a action, fantasy film directed by Gina Prince-Bythewood.
Four undying warriors who've secretly protected humanity for centuries become
targeted for their mysterious powers just as they discover a new immortal.
Andromache of Scythia / Andy, played by Charlize Theron.
Nile Freeman, played by KiKi Layne.
Quynh, played by Veronica Ngo.
Sebastien Le Livre / Booker, played by Matthias Schoenaerts.
Yusuf Al-Kaysani / Joe, played by Marwan Kenzari.
Nicolò di Genova / Nicky, played by Luca Marinelli.
The Old Guard is a 2020 American superhero film directed by Gina
Prince-Bythewood and written by Greg Rucka, based on his comic book series.
It stars Charlize Theron, KiKi Layne, Matthias Schoenaerts, Marwan Kenzari, Luca Marinelli, Harry Melling,
Veronica Ngo and Chiwetel Ejiofor, and follows a team of immortal mercenaries on a revenge mission.
It was released on July 10, 2020, on Netflix.
It received generally positive reviews, with praise for its
action sequences and Theron's performance.
A sequel directed by Victoria Mahoney, The Old
Guard 2, was released on July 2, 2025.
The film explores themes of immortality, superhero,
mercenary, based on comic, lgbt.